

Tümerkan Mustafa Durmuş

Software Engineer

I'm an engineer who places a high value on good communication and has extensive experience in developing userfriendly digital products. I take great joy in tackling complex tasks, employing the latest technologies, and being part of a dedicated team.

Work Experience

DB Systel, Frankfurt am Main

DevOps Engineer

Apr 2023 - Present

- Development of a web application for traffic management within a cross-functional, agile team
- Contribution to a cross-team component library
- Domain-Driven Design, Test-Driven Development

React - TypeScript - Spring Boot - Kotlin - GitLab CI/CD - OpenShift - Kubernetes - Docker - Prometheus - Grafana - AWS - Terraform

Student Jobs

Bosch Rexroth, Lohr am Main

Working student

Oct 2022 - Mar 2023

Development of a UI component library for control applications

Angular — TypeScript — Azure DevOps

Bosch Rexroth, Nürnberg

PreMaster

Oct 2021 - Sep 2022

Development of a web and mobile application for logistics processes

React — JavaScript — C# — .NET

Siemens Energy, Erlangen

Bachelorthesis

Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

Title: "Virtual Prototypes based on 3D Scans" — Grade: 1.3

Siemens Energy, Erlangen

Working student

Mar 2020 - Jan 2021

Development of a mobile app for live visualization of industrial data in augmented reality

Unity — C# — Python

Bosch Rexroth, Stuttgart

Intern

Mar 2019 - Aug 2019

Development of future-oriented Industry 4.0 projects (augmented reality, image recognition, machine learning)

Unity — HoloLens — C# — TensorFlow — Python

Contact

Nürnberg, Deutschland +4915236722290

tuemerkan.d@icloud.com

tuemerkan.dev

in linkedin.com/in/tuemerkan

@tuemerkan

Education

M.Sc. Computer Science

Oct 2022 - Present
Technische Hochschule Nürnberg

B. Eng. Media Engineering

Oct 2017 - Sep 2021 Technische Hochschule Nürnberg

Abitur

2016

Bertolt-Brecht-Gymnasium Nürnberg

Languages

German, Turkish native

English fluent

French intermediate

Hobbies

Fitnesstraining

Reading

Travel